https://www.wrestleview.com/privacy-policy

your password
Forgot your password?
your email
A password will be e-mailed to you.
WWE News and Results, RAW and Smackdown Results, Impact News, ROH News
PRIVACY POLICY
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which https://www.wrestleview.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the https://www.wrestleview.com/ website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by ENTER URL.
Personal identification information
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, subscribe to the newsletter, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
Non-personal identification information
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.
Web browser cookies
Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.
How we use collected information
www.wrestleview.com may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:
To improve customer service
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
To personalize user experience
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
To improve our Site
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature
To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
To send periodic emails
We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.
How we protect your information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.
Sharing your personal information
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.
Third party websites
Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensor and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.
Advertising
Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
Google Adsense
Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html
Changes to this privacy policy
www.wrestleview.com has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page and send you an email. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at: webmaster@wrestleview.com
LATEST PODCAST
WWE NEWS
Tommy “Tiny” Lister, best known as Zeus in WWF, passes away at 62
December 10, 2020
AEW Dynamite and WWE NXT Ratings: Dynamite is #2 show on cable for second week
December 10, 2020
WWE NXT Highlights: Karrion Kross Returns, Finn Balor draws challengers
December 10, 2020
WWE NXT Results – 12/9/20 (TakeOver: WarGames Fallout, NXT Star returns)
December 9, 2020
WWE looking for fans to show off their prized wrestling memorabilia
December 9, 2020
AEW NEWS
AEW CEO and President Tony Khan thanks fans for making Dynamite a ratings success
December 10, 2020
AEW Dynamite and WWE NXT Ratings: Dynamite is #2 show on cable for second week
December 10, 2020
AEW Dynamite Highlights: Sting Speaks, Kenny Omega and Don Callis, Shaq
December 10, 2020
AEW announces Dynamite Holiday Bash and New Year’s Smash Two-Night Event
December 10, 2020
Tony Khan announces huge 14-Man Tag Team Match for next week’s AEW Dynamite
December 10, 2020
WRESTLING RESULTS
AEW Dynamite Results – 12/9/20 (Sting speaks, Shaq, Kenny Omega, Inner Circle)
December 9, 2020
WWE NXT Results – 12/9/20 (TakeOver: WarGames Fallout, NXT Star returns)
December 9, 2020
IMPACT Results – 12/8/20 (Live Coverage, Kenny Omega and Tony Khan appear)
December 8, 2020
WWE Raw Results – 12/7/20 (Handicap Match Main Event, Orton on the Firefly Funhouse)
December 7, 2020
WWE SmackDown Results – 12/4/20 (Roman Reigns, Jey Uso vs. Kevin Owens, Otis, more)
December 4, 2020
ABOUT USWrestleview.com is your source for everything pro wrestling since 1997. Daily updates with WWE News, TNA News, Indy News and the latest Wrestling Results for WWE Raw, WWE Smackdown, TNA Impact Wrestling and more. Live coverage of WWE PPV and TNA PPV events. Plus, feature writers reviewing weekly wrestling shows, podcasts, wrestling information and more.FOLLOW US
© Privacy Policy | Wrestleview.com 1997 - 2019
